xeonbd.com 2010-01-14

# Privacy Policy - Xeon Software Limited

Privacy Policy

Xeon Software Limited is committed to protect the privacy of its customers. This privacy policy governs the manner in which Xeon Software Limited uses, maintains and discloses information collected from customers and users of Xeon Software Limited website. Xeon Software Limited is committed to develop long lasting relationships based on trust. Xeon Software Limited will do everything in its power to ensure that your right to privacy is maintained and protected. This privacy policy applies to the websites managed by Xeon Software Limited as well as the services and products provided through this site. From time to time we may make alterations to our website and to the products and services provided through it. This may result in periodic changes to the privacy policy. Any such changes will be posted on our website and we would ask that you refer back to it regularly in order to review any changes.

Use of the Xeon Software Limited's website and services indicates your consent to the collection and use of information as described below.

Any questions which you may have regarding this privacy policy should be directed to **::** [info@xeonbd.com](mailto:info@xeonbd.com) (info)

**1\. What information is collected and how is it used?**

The collected information will be used in the management of our own database and to enable Xeon Software Limited to contact you about the service you have requested (for example, to confirm the registration of a domain or hosting plan or to inform you of the need to renew your registration when it expires or to change information in any plan of Web Promotion and SEO). Information passed to Xeon Software Limited from your web browser may be stored and used in our internal statistical analysis. We may also automatically collect non-personal information about you such as the type of internet browsers you use or the site from which you linked to our website. You cannot be identified from this information and it is only used to assist us in providing an effective service on Xeon Software Limited's website.

**2\. Do we share the information with anyone else?**

Xeon Software Limited will not, without your consent, pass your personal information to a third party except in the following circumstances:

**(i)** If required to do so by law or by any organization with appropriate authority;

**(ii)** To any financial institution with whom we hold an account for the purpose of verifying credit status and / or validating financial transactions;

**(iii)** Xeon Software Limited may provide aggregate statistics about our sales, customers, traffic patterns and other site information to third parties, but these statistics will not include any information that could personally identify you;

**3\. Credit Cards**

Credit card payment for Xeon Software Limited's services is processed by [2Checkout.com](http://www.2checkout.com/ "2Checkout.com"), Inc. is an authorized retailer of goods and services provided by Xeon Software Limited. We do not record your credit card details on our database and the payment service provider does not record any other information about you.

**4\. How long will we hold data on you?**

Xeon Software Limited will not hold data for longer than is reasonably necessary for the purposes of the proper conduct of its business or as required by law.

**5\. Where is the data we hold stored?**

Information which you submit via Xeon Software Limited's website is stored on a computer and sometimes on paper at our offices. This is necessary in order to process the information and to send you any information you have requested.

**6\. Security**

Xeon Software Limited places great importance on the security of all information associated with its customers and has security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of customer data under our control. While we cannot ensure or guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of data will not occur, we use Xeon Software Limited best efforts to prevent this.

**7\. Links to Other Sites**

Xeon Software Limited website contains advertising and links to other websites. No personal information is passed to other websites if you follow one of these links. Xeon Software Limited is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of linked websites. We would encourage you to read the privacy statements of other websites, since their privacy policy may differ from Xeon Software Limited

**8\. Changes to Personal Information**

If you need to change the information that we keep, for example because you have moved or to correct an error, please contact us at **::** [info@xeonbd.com](mailto:info@xeonbd.com) (info)

**9\. Service Announcements**

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement, if, for instance, a domain registration or web hosting service is temporarily suspended for maintenance.

**10\. Your Responsibility**

You are responsible for the security of your Account Number and passwords. Make sure you keep it in a safe place and do not share it with others.

Always remember to log out after your session ends, to ensure that others cannot access your private personal information. You should take this precaution even if you are not using a public computer, such as at a library or internet café, but even when using your private computer in your home.

**11\. 30 Days Money Back**

If you are dissatisfied with 

_annual_

Linux hosting service, you may choose to cancel your subscription for a full refund. Only webhosting service covers this 30 Days Money Back policy. Domain name registration and additional services, all of which are non-refundable..

If you would like to cancel your account for any reason, then please contact Xeon Software Limited  Hosting billing department at: [billing@xeonbd.com](mailto:billing@xeonbd.com) .

30 Days Money Back Guarantee only valid for the clients sign up from Bangladesh and for getting your money back you must visit Xeon Software Limited's office.

_Clients outside of Bangladesh not eligible for 30 Days Money Back Guarantee in any condition_.

Any product purchase during the time of special promotion/special offer will not valid for 30 Days Money Back.

**Contact Information**

In the event of questions about access to your Personal Information or Prospect Information; our collection, use, management, or disclosure of Personal Information or Prospect Information; or this Privacy Statement, contact us at:

Xeon Software Limited  
Suite 2A, House 231, Road 06  
Mohammadi Housing Limited  
Mohammadpur, Dhaka 1207  
Bangladesh.

Hotline: +88 01977 936623 (XeonBD) 

**Effective Date**

This Privacy Statement is effective as of (GMT +06:00, Dhaka) June 18, 2008.

**Privacy Policy Version**

Version 1.3
